

UX DESIGNER

MAIN OBJECTIVE

I am a proactive UX Desginer with experience working on mobile apps and websites. My goal is to implement efficient and appealing designs for users based on an understanding of technology and collaboration with stakeholders and team members

CONTACT DETAILS

Cell: 323-895-0712

alicianunez.ux@gmail.com

alicianunez.github.io

💡 1858 S Dunsmuir Ave, Los Angeles, CA, 90019

DEVELOPMENT/DESIGN

- HTML/CSS, Javascript, Python
- React Native, Bootstrap
- Adobe XD, Figma, Marvel
- Github, Adobe Photoshop

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Wireframing, Prototyping, Storyboarding, Personas
- Cognitive Walkthroughs, Usability Testing
- Comparative Analysis, Interviews, Surveying

SOFT SKILLS

- Proficient Spanish Speaker
- Project Management
- Requirements Gathering

CERTIFICATE

BCG VIRTUAL EXPERIENCE PROGRAM 2020

- Completed Strategic and Experience Design modules.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OFFICE MANAGER

Santa Monica Auto Body | 2020 - present

- Communicated with insurance adjusters and assisted customers with insurance claims
- Used software to create and provide accurate estimates and supplements of vehicles.
- Managed the front desk and phone to provide assistance to customers in a professional and pleasant manner.
- Handled finances and city-mandated permits for the shop.

CAST MEMBER

Disneyland Resort | 2017 - 2019

- Provided personable guest service to a diverse guest base, while upholding company-wide standards.
- Demonstrated strong problem solving skills when confronted with guest requests and ride operation issues.
- Strived to ensure safety and create memorable experiences through guest control and interaction.

PUBLICITY CHAIR

Sigma Delta Sigma | 2018 - 2019

- In charge of logistics and managing event planning committees made up of various members .
- Designed flyers using Adobe Photoshop and advertised events through social media, reaching a large student body audience.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, IRVINE

BA in Informatics | 2020

- Specialization in Human-Computer Interaction.
- Minor in Linguistics.

YONSEI UNIVERSITY

Semester Abroad | 2019

INTERN PROJECTS

NEWS X-RAY (FACIAL RECOGNITION MOBILE APP)

University of California, Irvine | 2019

- Designed and implemented an app from scratch that uses facial recognition to identify political pundits.
- Created wireframes on Adobe XD and then developed the app's front-end using the React Native framework.
- Held user testing sessions and engaged in other research methods to better understand our clientele.